backgroundalert.com 2016-05-10

# background checks: criminal, arrest, marriage/divorce, public records, court records

Updated July 5th, 2013 

* * *

##### We Respect Your Privacy

At BackgroundAlert.com®, your security is a top priority and we are committed to protecting your privacy online. This pledge outlines the steps we've taken to ensure that you have a great experience at BackgroundAlert.com, and also provides details on how we treat any personal information you may submit to us.

##### Information Collection and Use

We will collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through this website. We will also collect information in order to notify you about products, services, and other opportunities we think will be of interest to you. Although personal information we collect from you may be considered publicly available through government records or available through widely distributed media, we will treat all personal information submitted by you as nonpublic personal information. The information we collect may be from the following sources: 

  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining financial products or services such as mortgage loans (such as full name, telephone number, self-assessed property value, and social security number).
  * Information you provide us when you register to receive communications from us (such as your email address).
  * Information you provide us when you enter promotions or sweepstakes offered by BackgroundAlert.com (such as your full name, physical address and email address).
  * Information you provide us through surveys, feedback, or other forms hosted on our website or the pages of a BackgroundAlert.com partner.
  * Information you provide us when you apply for a job with BackgroundAlert.com.

We also collect demographic information. Demographic information is all other information such as gender, zip code, or any information that is not tied to your personal information. In addition, we might receive information about you from other sources (such as service providers) for tracking purposes. We may add the information we receive about you to your existing account. Like other websites, we also automatically receive and record certain types of information every time you visit us. We use "cookies" and the other information to enhance your experience and present you with personalized offers. Likewise, we sometimes use third-party advertising companies to serve and track advertisements appearing on our website. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not share personal information about you with other people or non affiliated companies except to provide product or services you have requested or under the following circumstances: 

##### Data Products Searches or Service Requests

If you submit a search request for a data product or service offered through this website, we will share information contained in your search request (not your personal information) with our data providers to fulfill your request. All data providers are required to comply with federal and state privacy regulations. 

##### Vendors

We sometimes disclose the information we collect to companies that host certain services for us such as marketing distribution services on our behalf. These vendors only have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and may not share it with others or use it for any other purpose. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit them from using the information except to market the specified BackgroundAlert.com products or services. 

##### As Permitted by Law

We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of BackgroundAlert.com's Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 

##### Business Transfer

As with any other business, it is possible that BackgroundAlert.com in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by BackgroundAlert.com, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this privacy pledge unless you consent otherwise. 

##### Advertisements & Pop Up Windows

On occasion, you may receive advertisements for BackgroundAlert.com from third parties. For instance, when visiting a third party website, you may receive a "pop up" window advertising BackgroundAlert.com. Please note that such advertisements are served by the third party website that you have visited and are not controlled by BackgroundAlert.com. In addition, such advertisements may be placed by third party ad servers or ad networks. In certain instances our web banner advertisements may make a server call to data.innovativemetrics.com for data that will be used in the ad. This server may use your IP address to determine geo data and display advertisements that are targeted to your geo location. This server does not collect any data nor does it set any tracking cookies. We maintain relationships with a number of the third party ad networks currently operating. You may find more information at the website of either the individual ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative.

##### Anti-Spam Policy

You will not receive BackgroundAlert.com email communications unless you submit your email address to us and register to receive them. Additionally, you may also receive emails that advertise BackgroundAlert.com's services from third party publishers. We have established firm ground rules for dealing with any third party email services to ensure that advertisements for BackgroundAlert.com are not sent out through a "Spam" mailing -- ensuring that our offers are sent only to those individuals who have given their permission to the third party email service to receive email communications. If any third party email publisher refuses to abide by BackgroundAlert.com's anti-Spam policy, we will not use that publisher's services. If you want to stop receiving emails from a third party, you should follow the opt-out instructions included in the third party email so that you will not be included in any future mailings. An "unsubscribe" link should appear within or at the top or bottom of the email you received. However if for any reason it does not work, please bring that to our attention by emailing us at BackgroundAlert.com Customer Care. 

##### Cookies and IP Addresses

To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Website to "personalize" itself for each user. We generally use cookies to reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer and to assist with customer tracking. Customer tracking (or "click-stream") data collected by us is used to optimize your experience by learning whether or not you successfully used BackgroundAlert.com. Cookies are not tied to your personal information. Additionally, we may capture click-stream data on some of our partner's websites, limited to the activity involved with the completion of offers listed on our website. This information is used to monitor the performance of our partners. 

We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 

##### Third Party Cookies

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.fetcharate.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

##### Clear Gifs

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movement of Web users. Clear gifs are not tied to users' personally identifiable information. We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section within any email you receive from us or unsubscribe from our homepage by clicking here. 

##### Confidentiality and Security

The security of your personal information is very important at BackgroundAlert.com and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example: 

  * We limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who assist us in providing requested products and services to you. Employees are required to comply with our strict policies and procedures regarding the handling of your personal information. Employees who violate these policies are subject to our normal disciplinary process.
  * We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard personal information about you.
  * We use industry standard data encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data on the BackgroundAlert.com website.
  * We have partnered with VeriSign to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we collect from you.

##### Changes to Your Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at info@BackgroundAlert.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

##### Opting-Out

You may register to receive communications from us directly on our website or through a third party. Upon registering, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails featuring special and exclusive offers, promotions and other members-only benefits. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to BackgroundAlert.com Customer Care (You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails). Our email database is updated continually. However, you may continue to receive email communications from us up to ten business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. Please note that BackgroundAlert.com can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications. Also, please note that if you enter into a transaction through our website, we may send you a thank you notice, ask for a satisfaction rating, request a testimonial and give you periodic product reminders as part of your service. 

##### Third Party Links

This Privacy Pledge applies to all information that you provide to BackgroundAlert.com. However, when you visit websites to which BackgroundAlert.com provides a link, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party's privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. 

If BackgroundAlert.com receives personal information from a third party that is not in conjunction with a service offered on our site, the use and disclosure of such information is governed by the agreement (if any) between BackgroundAlert.com and such third party. 

##### Third Party Cookies

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.fetcharate.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

##### Framing

In some cases, we may use third party vendors to operate portions of the BackgroundAlert.com website. Although the particular section of the website may have a similar appearance as the BackgroundAlert.com site, information submitted through these outside third parties are subject to this Privacy Pledge unless otherwise stated. For example, personal information submitted through our Affiliate Program is subject to the Commission Junction privacy policy. 

##### A Special Note about Children's Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our website only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms of Use for more information. 

##### Changes to this Privacy Pledge

BackgroundAlert.com may update or modify this Privacy Pledge from time to time. If there are material changes to this Privacy Pledge or in how BackgroundAlert.com will use your personal information, we will post such changes here. You will be notified if any of the material changes that affect the use of your personal information and asked to opt-in to the new use of your personal information. If you do not agree with the changes to how your information will be used, please do not continue to use this website. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the BackgroundAlert.com Privacy Pledge. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any of the BackgroundAlert.com site. When you request rate quotes or other information through BackgroundAlert.com, you are authorizing us to share information with a lender or one of our business partners, who will contact you by phone, email, or mail. If you do not want further communication from them, please notify the partner directly. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Pledge will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Pledge. 

##### Our Referral Service

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. BackgroundAlert.com does not store this information. 

##### Supplemental Information Form Outside Sources

In order to provide certain services [specify] to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. 

* Address Verification - We may use TargusInfo to verify your identity, address, for quality data validation only.

* Enhancement of Profile Information - We purchase marketing data from third parties and add it to our existing user database, to better target our advertising and to provide pertinent offers in which we think you would be interested. To enrich our Profiles of individual customers, we tie this information to the personally identifiable information they have provided to us.

BackgroundAlert.com   
9692 Melinda Circle   
Huntington Beach, CA 92646
